

#### **CONTACT**

PHONE: 00966540002139

EMAIL:

Lulu.k@almisfer.com

#### **EDUCATION**

- **-King Saud University (KSU) -**MA in management and planning -2016
- -Imam Mohammed Ibn Saudi Islamic University (IMSIU)- MA in counselling and career guidance
- **King Saud University (KSU)** B.A in Psychology

# LULWAH KHALID ALMISFER

## **PROFILE**

An accomplished professional in PM, project and program portfolio management with considerable experience as a customer account manager in projects and event management. Impressive track record of successful technical proposals to the world's leading companies. Considerable experience in CRM, PR and marketing over more than seven years of hands-on experience, ably organized and managed more than 40 events and conferences for various government agencies, effective communication skills and cultivating profound official and professional relationships.

#### **SKILLS**

- Professional Project Management
- Teamwork management
- Effective communications skills
- Multitasking skills
- Marketing skills
- Event and exhibition management
- Budget management
- Systemic thinking
- Hospitability industry skills
- Fast learner

#### **ACCOMPLISHMENTS**

- Delivered more than 20 training courses in wide- raining areas including management, marketing and customer quotations.
- Developed Come and do PM process and procedures.
- Designed job description for PM processes, task assignment for COMEAND DO team
- Participate as organization reprehensive in Dubai Expo 2021, FORMELA1, and many events and conferences.

#### **CAREER**

#### March 2020- Present

(Seera Group)

#### Senior manager account

- Managing business to business B to B as well as Governmental G to G sectors in order to expand portfolio of strategic relationships.
- Follow up logistic needs of clients, operation team and administrations work including payments of clients.
- Developing Request for Proposal RFP, Technically and financially sides in terms of matching both ETMAD platform standers, and corporation's needs.

#### March 2019- Feb 2021 (COME AND DO)

#### Customer account manager

- Management business sector accounts, more than 25 (government agencies).
- Development strategic partnerships with government agencies to carry out projects in alignment with the kingdom's vision.
- Developing local content and promoting Saudi culture in projects delivered.
- Creating an annual plan targeting project.
- Preparing presentations for event contents and operational plan.
  Leading and supervising project management, task assignments and power delegation (3 project managers).

## April 2017- Feb 2019 MINISTRY OF COMMERCE

# Planning Unit Manager (Customer Service Department)

- managing and raising the efficiency the quality of 72 services provided by ministry of commerce (CRM).
- Handling, analyzing and directing to the competent department the incoming complaints through Reports and Complaints System

#### Sept 2015-Jan 2017 EMMAR ENGINEERING

## Assistant Project Manager

- Following up technical and financial projects to public and private entities.
- Organizing , coordinating and scheduling meetings .

- Closely monitoring technical team to ensure fulfilling the requirements of each milestone.

# Feb 2013- Aug 2015 EMMAR ENGINEERING

## PR Manager

- Cultivating and deepening corporate relationships with public and private sectors.
- Developing and increasing Emaar effective participations and contributions in exhibitions and conventions.
- Responsible protocol of visiting delegations, arranging and coordinating visit programs.
- Organizing media campaigns that better serve the marketing plan.
- Building and executing employee programs for creating dynamic work environment.

# TRAINING COURSES

COURSE TITLE	DATE & duration
Effective leader program	2019 (5) days
Work process management	2019 (3) days
Banking industry concept and role in Economic	2018- (5) days
Development – financial institute	
Enterprise Performance measurement skills	2018- (3) days
Google Search Engine marketing	2018 (2) days

Documents are available upon request